emobilez.com 2010-06-23

# Privacy Policy | Terms of use

## Privacy Policy

Please read carefully Privacy Policy for this site. 

All downloads are for personal use only, this site is not responsible for the contents of them. All downloads are freeware; if not, write a mail to communicate the technical-problem and the file will be deleted immediately. The author intended not to use any copyrighted material for the publication or, if not possible, to indicate the copyright of the respective object. eMobilez.com will not be held liable for any damages as a result of the free stuff/file you download. We do our best to ensure the safety of our members, and strive to make sure that no files on our server contain any virus or spy ware, but if one does slip through, be advised we will not be held responsible. If there is any problem with this download, aside from functionality or usage of the work, please report this file to webmaster for review. The author reserves the right not to be responsible for the topicality, correctness, completeness or quality of the information provided. Liability claims regarding damage caused by the use of any information provided, including any kind of information which is incomplete or incorrect, will therefore be rejected.

EMOBILEZ.COM DOES NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATION REGARDING THE USE, OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE, OF FILES / FREE STUFF IN TERMS OF CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, CORRECTNESS, OR OTHERWISE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF THE DOWNLOADS IS ASSUMED BY THE END USER. EMOBILEZ.COM SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO END USER FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES ARISING FROM THESE FREE STUFF PROVIDED ON OUR SITE. You are downloading FREE STUFF OR File at your own free will, and that you assume any and all responsibilities incorporated in doing so.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We also use third party advertisements on our site to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

#### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

#### Valueclickmedia

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>
